<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.speedcrunch.SpeedCrunch</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <update_contact>speedcrunch@googlegroups.com</update_contact>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0"/>

  
  <name>SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="es_AR">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_PT">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="uz@Latn">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh">SpeedCrunch</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">SpeedCrunch</name>
  
  <summary>A high-precision scientific calculator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">آلة حاسبة علمية عالية الدقة</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Una calculadora científica d'alta precisió</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Vysoce přesná vědecká kalkulačka</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">En videnskabelig lommeregner med høj præcision</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein hochpräziser wissenschaftlicher Taschenrechner</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Επιστημονική αριθμομηχανή υψηλής ακρίβειας</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">A high-precision scientific calculator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Altpreciza scienca kalkulilo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una calculadora científica de alta precisión</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es_AR">Una calculadora científica de alta precisión</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Kõrgtäpne teaduslik kalkulaator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Zehaztasun handiko kalkulagailu zientifikoa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">ماشین‌حساب علمی با دقت بالا</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Erittäin tarkka tieteellinen laskin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Une calculatrice scientifique de haute précision</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מחשבון מדעי בדיוק גבוה</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Egy nagy pontosságú tudományos számológép</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Kalkulator ilmiah presisi tinggi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Una calcolatrice scientifica ad alta precisione</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">高精度の科学計算機</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">고정밀 공학용 계산기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Labai tikslus mokslinis skaičiuotuvas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Augstas precizitātes zinātniskais kalkulators</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">En vitenskapelig kalkulator med høy presisjon</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een wetenschappelijke rekenmachine met hoge precisie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wysokoprecyzyjny kalkulator naukowy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Calculadora científica de alta precisão</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_PT">Uma calculadora científica de alta precisão</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Un calculator științific de înaltă precizie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Научный инженерный калькулятор</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Vysokopresná vedecká kalkulačka</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Visokonatančen znanstveni kalkulator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">En vetenskaplig miniräknare med hög precision</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Yüksek hassasiyetli bilimsel hesap makinesi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Високоточний науковий калькулятор</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uz@Latn">Yuqori aniqlikdagi ilmiy kalkulyator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Máy tính khoa học có độ chính xác cao</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh">高精度科学计算器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">高精度科學計算器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>SpeedCrunch is a fast, high-precision scientific calculator. It features a syntax-highlighted scrollable display and is designed to be fully used via keyboard.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">SpeedCrunch آلة حاسبة علمية سريعة وعالية الدقة. تتميز بعرض قابل للتمرير مع إبراز بناء الجملة، وهي مصممة ليُستخدم البرنامج بالكامل عبر لوحة المفاتيح.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">SpeedCrunch és una calculadora científica ràpida i d'alta precisió. Inclou una pantalla desplaçable amb ressaltat de sintaxi i està dissenyada per ser utilitzada completament amb el teclat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">SpeedCrunch je rychlá, vysoce přesná vědecká kalkulačka. Nabízí rolovatelný displej se zvýrazněním syntaxe a je navržena pro plné ovládání z klávesnice.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">SpeedCrunch er en hurtig, videnskabelig lommeregner med høj præcision. Den har et rullebart display med syntaksfremhævning og er designet til at kunne bruges fuldt ud via tastaturet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">SpeedCrunch ist ein schneller, hochpräziser, wissenschaftlicher Taschenrechner. Es bietet eine scrollbare Anzeige mit Syntaxhervorhebung und ist auf vollständige Tastaturbedienung ausgelegt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το SpeedCrunch είναι μια γρήγορη επιστημονική αριθμομηχανή υψηλής ακρίβειας. Διαθέτει κυλιόμενη οθόνη με επισήμανση σύνταξης και έχει σχεδιαστεί ώστε να χρησιμοποιείται πλήρως από το πληκτρολόγιο.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">SpeedCrunch is a fast, high-precision scientific calculator. It features a syntax-highlighted scrollable display and is designed to be fully used via keyboard.SpeedCrunch is a fast, high-precision scientific calculator. It features a syntax-highlighted scrollable display and is designed to be fully used via keyboard.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">SpeedCrunch estas rapida, altpreciza scienca kalkulilo. Ĝi havas rulumeblan ekranon kun sintaksemfazo kaj estas desegnita por esti uzata plene per klavaro.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">SpeedCrunch es una calculadora científica rápida y de alta precisión. Cuenta con una pantalla desplazable con resaltado de sintaxis y está diseñada para usarse completamente con el teclado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es_AR">SpeedCrunch es una calculadora científica rápida y de alta precisión. Cuenta con una pantalla desplazable con resaltado de sintaxis y está diseñada para usarse completamente con el teclado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">SpeedCrunch on kiire ja kõrgtäpne teaduslik kalkulaator. Sellel on süntaksi esiletõstuga keritav kuva ning see on loodud täielikult klaviatuuriga kasutamiseks.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">SpeedCrunch zehaztasun handiko kalkulagailu zientifiko azkarra da. Sintaxia nabarmenduta duen bistaratze korritzailea dauka, eta teklatu bidez erabat erabiltzeko diseinatuta dago.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">SpeedCrunch یک ماشین‌حساب علمی سریع و با دقت بالاست. این برنامه دارای نمایشگر قابل‌پیمایش با برجسته‌سازی نحو است و برای استفادهٔ کامل از طریق صفحه‌کلید طراحی شده است.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">SpeedCrunch on nopea ja erittäin tarkka tieteellinen laskin. Siinä on syntaksikorostettu vieritettävä näyttö, ja se on suunniteltu käytettäväksi kokonaan näppäimistöllä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">SpeedCrunch est une calculatrice scientifique rapide et de haute précision. Elle propose un affichage défilant avec coloration syntaxique et est conçue pour être utilisée entièrement au clavier.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">SpeedCrunch הוא מחשבון מדעי מהיר ובדיוק גבוה. הוא כולל תצוגה נגללת עם הדגשת תחביר, ונועד לשימוש מלא באמצעות המקלדת.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A SpeedCrunch egy gyors, nagy pontosságú tudományos számológép. Szintaxis kiemeléses, görgethető kijelzővel rendelkezik és úgy tervezték, hogy teljes mértékben használható legyen billentyűzetről.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">SpeedCrunch adalah kalkulator ilmiah yang cepat dan berpresisi tinggi. Aplikasi ini memiliki tampilan yang dapat digulir dengan penyorotan sintaks, dan dirancang untuk digunakan sepenuhnya melalui papan ketik.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">SpeedCrunch è una calcolatrice scientifica veloce e ad alta precisione. Presenta uno schermo scorrevole con evidenziazione della sintassi ed è progettata per essere completamente usabile tramite tastiera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">SpeedCrunch は高速で高精度な科学計算機です。構文強調表示付きのスクロール可能な表示を備え、キーボードだけで完全に操作できるよう設計されています。</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">SpeedCrunch는 빠르고 고정밀인 공학용 계산기입니다. 구문 강조 표시가 적용된 스크롤 가능한 화면을 제공하며, 키보드만으로 완전히 사용할 수 있도록 설계되었습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">SpeedCrunch yra greitas, labai tikslus mokslinis skaičiuotuvas. Jis pasižymi sintaksę paryškinančiu slenkančiu ekranu ir yra sukurtas, kad būtų pilnai naudojamas su klaviatūra.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">SpeedCrunch ir ātrs, augstas precizitātes zinātniskais kalkulators. Tam ir ritināms displejs ar sintakses izcelšanu, un tas ir paredzēts pilnīgai lietošanai ar tastatūru.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">SpeedCrunch er en rask vitenskapelig kalkulator med høy presisjon. Den har et rullbart display med syntaksutheving og er utviklet for å kunne brukes fullt ut med tastaturet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">SpeedCrunch is een snelle wetenschappelijke rekenmachine met hoge precisie. Het beschikt over een scrollbaar scherm met syntaxisaccentuering en is ontworpen om volledig via het toetsenbord te worden gebruikt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">SpeedCrunch to szybki, wysokoprecyzyjny kalkulator naukowy. Posiada przewijalny ekran z podświetlaniem składni i jest zaprojektowany do pełnej obsługi z klawiatury.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O SpeedCrunch é uma calculadora científica rápida e de alta precisão. Ele possui um visor rolável com realce de sintaxe e foi projetado para ser usado totalmente pelo teclado.SpeedCrunch é uma calculadora científica rápida e de alta precisão. Ela possui um mostrador rolável, com destaque de sintaxe e é concebida para ser plenamente utilizável através do teclado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_PT">O SpeedCrunch é uma calculadora científica rápida e de alta precisão. Apresenta um visor rolável com realce de sintaxe e foi concebido para ser utilizado integralmente através do teclado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">SpeedCrunch este un calculator științific rapid, de înaltă precizie. Oferă un afișaj derulabil cu evidențiere a sintaxei și este conceput pentru a fi folosit în întregime de la tastatură.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">SpeedCrunch — быстрый высокоточный научный калькулятор. Он имеет прокручиваемый дисплей с подсветкой синтаксиса и предназначен для полного управления с клавиатуры.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">SpeedCrunch je rýchla, vysoko presná vedecká kalkulačka. Ponúka rolovateľný displej so zvýraznením syntaxe a je navrhnutá tak, aby sa dala plnohodnotne používať pomocou klávesnice.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">SpeedCrunch je hiter, visokonatančen znanstveni kalkulator. Ima pomično prikazovalno okno s poudarjanjem skladnje in je zasnovan za popolno uporabo s tipkovnico.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">SpeedCrunch är en snabb vetenskaplig miniräknare med hög precision. Den har en rullbar skärm med syntaxmarkering och är utformad för att kunna användas helt via tangentbordet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">SpeedCrunch hızlı ve yüksek hassasiyetli bir bilimsel hesap makinesidir. Sözdizimi vurgulamalı kaydırılabilir bir ekrana sahiptir ve tamamen klavye ile kullanılacak şekilde tasarlanmıştır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">SpeedCrunch — швидкий високоточний науковий калькулятор. Він має прокручуваний дисплей із підсвічуванням синтаксису та призначений для повного використання з клавіатури.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uz@Latn">SpeedCrunch tezkor va yuqori aniqlikdagi ilmiy kalkulyator. Unda sintaksis yoritilgan, aylantiriladigan displey mavjud va u to'liq klaviatura orqali foydalanish uchun mo'ljallangan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">SpeedCrunch là một máy tính khoa học nhanh và có độ chính xác cao. Ứng dụng có màn hình cuộn với tô sáng cú pháp và được thiết kế để có thể sử dụng hoàn toàn bằng bàn phím.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh">SpeedCrunch 是一个快速、高精度的科学计算器。它具有语法高亮和可滚动的显示，并且可以全程使用键盘操作。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">SpeedCrunch 是一款快速且高精度的科學計算器。它具備語法醒目提示的可捲動顯示，並且設計為可完全透過鍵盤操作。</p>

    <p>It includes many built-in maths functions and supports advanced features like user-defined functions, complex numbers, and unit conversions. This is combined with a simple yet powerful user interface featuring on-the-fly results preview, syntax highlighting, and autocompletion.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يتضمن العديد من الدوال الرياضية المضمنة ويدعم ميزات متقدمة مثل الدوال المعرّفة من قبل المستخدم، والأعداد المركبة، وتحويل الوحدات. ويتكامل ذلك مع واجهة مستخدم بسيطة لكنها قوية تتضمن معاينة فورية للنتائج، وإبراز بناء الجملة، والإكمال التلقائي.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Inclou moltes funcions matemàtiques integrades i admet funcions avançades com les funcions definides per l'usuari, els nombres complexos i les conversions d'unitats. Tot això es combina amb una interfície d'usuari senzilla però potent amb previsualització de resultats al vol, ressaltat de sintaxi i autocompleció.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Obsahuje mnoho vestavěných matematických funkcí a podporuje pokročilé funkce, jako jsou uživatelsky definované funkce, komplexní čísla a převody jednotek. To vše doplňuje jednoduché, ale výkonné uživatelské rozhraní s okamžitým náhledem výsledků, zvýrazněním syntaxe a automatickým doplňováním.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Den indeholder mange indbyggede matematiske funktioner og understøtter avancerede funktioner såsom brugerdefinerede funktioner, komplekse tal og enhedskonverteringer. Dette kombineres med en enkel, men kraftfuld brugerflade med forhåndsvisning af resultater i realtid, syntaksfremhævning og autofuldførelse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Es enthält viele eingebaute Mathematikfunktionen und unterstützt fortgeschrittene Funktionen wie benutzerdefinierte Funktionen, komplexe Zahlen und Einheitenumwandlungen. Dies ist verbunden mit einer einfacher, aber leistungsfähigen Benutzeroberfläche mit dynamischer Ergebnisvorschau, Syntaxhervorhebung und automatischer Vervollständigung.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Περιλαμβάνει πολλές ενσωματωμένες μαθηματικές συναρτήσεις και υποστηρίζει προηγμένες δυνατότητες όπως συναρτήσεις ορισμένες από τον χρήστη, μιγαδικούς αριθμούς και μετατροπές μονάδων. Όλα αυτά συνδυάζονται με ένα απλό αλλά ισχυρό περιβάλλον χρήστη με προεπισκόπηση αποτελεσμάτων σε πραγματικό χρόνο, επισήμανση σύνταξης και αυτόματη συμπλήρωση.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">It includes many built-in maths functions and supports advanced features like user-defined functions, complex numbers, and unit conversions. This is combined with a simple yet powerful user interface featuring on-the-fly results preview, syntax highlighting, and autocompletion.It includes many built-in maths functions and supports advanced features like user-defined functions, complex numbers, and unit conversions. This is combined with a simple yet powerful user interface featuring on-the-fly results preview, syntax highlighting, and autocompletion.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Ĝi enhavas multajn enkonstruitajn matematikajn funkciojn kaj subtenas altnivelajn ecojn kiel uzantodifinitajn funkciojn, kompleksajn nombrojn kaj unuokonvertojn. Ĉio ĉi estas kombinita kun simpla sed potenca uzantinterfaco kun tuja antaŭrigardo de rezultoj, sintaksemfazo kaj aŭtomata kompletigo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Incluye muchas funciones matemáticas integradas y admite funciones avanzadas como funciones definidas por el usuario, números complejos y conversiones de unidades. Todo ello se combina con una interfaz de usuario sencilla pero potente que ofrece vista previa de resultados al vuelo, resaltado de sintaxis y autocompletado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es_AR">Incluye muchas funciones matemáticas integradas y admite funciones avanzadas como funciones definidas por el usuario, números complejos y conversiones de unidades. Todo ello se combina con una interfaz de usuario sencilla pero potente que ofrece vista previa de resultados al vuelo, resaltado de sintaxis y autocompletado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">See sisaldab palju sisseehitatud matemaatikafunktsioone ja toetab täiustatud võimalusi, nagu kasutaja määratud funktsioonid, kompleksarvud ja ühikute teisendused. Seda kõike ühendab lihtne, kuid võimas kasutajaliides, mis pakub tulemuste kohest eelvaadet, süntaksi esiletõstu ja automaatset lõpetamist.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Matematika-funtzio integratu ugari ditu, eta eginbide aurreratuak onartzen ditu, hala nola erabiltzaileak definitutako funtzioak, zenbaki konplexuak eta unitate-bihurketak. Hori guztia erabiltzaile-interfaze sinple baina indartsu batekin uztartzen da, emaitzen aurrebista berehalakoa, sintaxi-nabarmendua eta osatze automatikoa eskainiz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">این برنامه شامل بسیاری از توابع ریاضیِ داخلی است و از قابلیت‌های پیشرفته‌ای مانند توابعِ تعریف‌شده توسط کاربر، اعداد مختلط و تبدیل واحدها پشتیبانی می‌کند. همهٔ این‌ها با یک رابط کاربری ساده اما قدرتمند همراه است که پیش‌نمایشِ آنیِ نتایج، برجسته‌سازیِ نحو و تکمیل خودکار را فراهم می‌کند.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Se sisältää monia sisäänrakennettuja matemaattisia toimintoja ja tukee edistyneitä ominaisuuksia, kuten käyttäjän määrittelemiä funktioita, kompleksilukuja ja yksikkömuunnoksia. Tämä yhdistyy yksinkertaiseen mutta tehokkaaseen käyttöliittymään, jossa on tulosten reaaliaikainen esikatselu, syntaksikorostus ja automaattinen täydennys.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Elle inclut de nombreuses fonctions mathématiques intégrées et prend en charge des fonctionnalités avancées comme les fonctions définies par l'utilisateur, les nombres complexes et les conversions d'unités. Le tout est associé à une interface simple mais puissante offrant l'aperçu des résultats à la volée, la coloration syntaxique et l'autocomplétion.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">הוא כולל פונקציות מתמטיות מובנות רבות ותומך בתכונות מתקדמות כמו פונקציות בהגדרת משתמש, מספרים מרוכבים והמרות יחידות. כל זאת משולב עם ממשק משתמש פשוט אך עוצמתי הכולל תצוגה מקדימה של תוצאות בזמן אמת, הדגשת תחביר והשלמה אוטומטית.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Számos beépített matematikai függvényt tartalmaz és támogatja az olyan fejlett képességeket, mint a felhasználó által biztosított függvények, komplex számok és a mértékegység konvertálás. Mindez kombinálva van egy egyszerű, de fejlett felhasználói felülettel, ami lehetővé teszi az eredmények azonnali előnézetét, szintaxis kiemelést és az automatikus kiegészítést.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Aplikasi ini mencakup banyak fungsi matematika bawaan dan mendukung fitur lanjutan seperti fungsi yang ditentukan pengguna, bilangan kompleks, dan konversi satuan. Semuanya dipadukan dengan antarmuka pengguna yang sederhana namun kuat, dengan pratinjau hasil secara langsung, penyorotan sintaks, dan pelengkapan otomatis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Include molte funzioni matematiche predefinite e supporta funzionalità avanzate come funzioni definite dall'utente, numeri complessi e conversione di unità. Questo si aggiunge ad un'interfaccia utente semplice ma potente che fornisce anteprime al volo dei risultati, evidenziazione della sintassi ed autocompletamento. </p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">多数の組み込み数学関数を備え、ユーザー定義関数、複素数、単位変換などの高度な機能をサポートします。さらに、結果のリアルタイムプレビュー、構文強調表示、自動補完を備えたシンプルかつ強力なユーザーインターフェースと組み合わされています。</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">다양한 내장 수학 함수를 포함하고 사용자 정의 함수, 복소수, 단위 변환과 같은 고급 기능을 지원합니다. 또한 결과의 실시간 미리보기, 구문 강조 표시, 자동 완성을 갖춘 단순하면서도 강력한 사용자 인터페이스를 제공합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Jame yra įtaisytos daugelis matematinių funkcijų ir jis palaiko tokias išplėstines funkcijas kaip naudotojo apibrėžtos funkcijos, kompleksiniai skaičiai ir vienetų konvertavimai. Tai yra sujungta su paprasta, tačiau galinga naudotojo sąsaja, kuri pasižymi žaibiškai greita rezultatų peržiūra, sintaksės paryškinimu ir automatiniu užbaigimu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Tas ietver daudzas iebūvētas matemātiskās funkcijas un atbalsta uzlabotas iespējas, piemēram, lietotāja definētas funkcijas, kompleksos skaitļus un vienību pārveidošanu. To papildina vienkārša, bet jaudīga lietotāja saskarne ar rezultātu priekšskatījumu reāllaikā, sintakses izcelšanu un automātisko pabeigšanu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Den inneholder mange innebygde matematiske funksjoner og støtter avanserte funksjoner som brukerdefinerte funksjoner, komplekse tall og enhetskonverteringer. Dette kombineres med et enkelt, men kraftig brukergrensesnitt med forhåndsvisning av resultater i sanntid, syntaksutheving og autofullføring.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het bevat veel ingebouwde wiskundige functies en ondersteunt geavanceerde functies zoals door de gebruiker gedefinieerde functies, complexe getallen en eenheidsconversies. Dit wordt gecombineerd met een eenvoudige maar krachtige gebruikersinterface met live voorbeeld van resultaten, syntaxisaccentuering en automatisch aanvullen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Zawiera wiele wbudowanych funkcji matematycznych i obsługuje zaawansowane możliwości, takie jak funkcje definiowane przez użytkownika, liczby zespolone i konwersje jednostek. Wszystko to połączono z prostym, a zarazem potężnym interfejsem użytkownika oferującym podgląd wyników na bieżąco, podświetlanie składni i autouzupełnianie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Inclui muitas funções matemáticas integradas e oferece suporte a recursos avançados como funções definidas pelo usuário, números complexos e conversões de unidades. Isso é combinado com uma interface de usuário simples, porém poderosa, com pré-visualização de resultados em tempo real, realce de sintaxe e autocompletar.Ela inclui muitas funções matemáticas embutidas e suporta características avançadas como funções definidas pelo usuário, números complexos e conversão de unidades. Isso combinado a uma poderosa interface com resultados instantâneos, destaque de sintaxe e auto completação.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_PT">Inclui muitas funções matemáticas integradas e suporta funcionalidades avançadas, como funções definidas pelo utilizador, números complexos e conversões de unidades. Isto é combinado com uma interface de utilizador simples, mas poderosa, com pré-visualização de resultados em tempo real, realce de sintaxe e conclusão automática.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Include multe funcții matematice integrate și acceptă funcționalități avansate, precum funcții definite de utilizator, numere complexe și conversii de unități. Toate acestea sunt combinate cu o interfață de utilizator simplă, dar puternică, cu previzualizare a rezultatelor în timp real, evidențiere a sintaxei și completare automată.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Он включает множество встроенных математических функций и поддерживает расширенные возможности, такие как пользовательские функции, комплексные числа и преобразование единиц. Всё это сочетается с простым, но мощным интерфейсом с мгновенным предпросмотром результатов, подсветкой синтаксиса и автодополнением.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Obsahuje veľa vstavaných matematických funkcií a podporuje pokročilé funkcie, ako sú používateľom definované funkcie, komplexné čísla a prevody jednotiek. To je kombinované s jednoduchým, no výkonným používateľským rozhraním s priebežným náhľadom výsledkov, zvýraznením syntaxe a automatickým dopĺňaním.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Vključuje veliko vgrajenih matematičnih funkcij in podpira napredne zmožnosti, kot so uporabniško določene funkcije, kompleksna števila in pretvorbe enot. To je združeno s preprostim, a zmogljivim uporabniškim vmesnikom z sprotnim predogledom rezultatov, poudarjanjem skladnje in samodokončevanjem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Den innehåller många inbyggda matematiska funktioner och stöder avancerade funktioner som användardefinierade funktioner, komplexa tal och enhetsomvandlingar. Detta kombineras med ett enkelt men kraftfullt användargränssnitt med förhandsvisning av resultat i realtid, syntaxmarkering och automatisk komplettering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Birçok yerleşik matematik işlevi içerir ve kullanıcı tanımlı işlevler, karmaşık sayılar ve birim dönüştürmeleri gibi gelişmiş özellikleri destekler. Bunlar, anlık sonuç önizlemesi, sözdizimi vurgulama ve otomatik tamamlama sunan basit ama güçlü bir kullanıcı arayüzü ile birleşir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Він містить багато вбудованих математичних функцій і підтримує розширені можливості, такі як визначені користувачем функції, комплексні числа та перетворення одиниць. Це поєднано з простим, але потужним інтерфейсом користувача з миттєвим попереднім переглядом результатів, підсвічуванням синтаксису та автодоповненням.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uz@Latn">U ko'plab ichki matematik funksiyalarni o'z ichiga oladi va foydalanuvchi tomonidan belgilangan funksiyalar, kompleks sonlar hamda birliklarni o'zgartirish kabi ilg'or imkoniyatlarni qo'llab-quvvatlaydi. Bularning barchasi natijalarni darhol oldindan ko'rish, sintaksisni yoritish va avtomatik to'ldirish kabi funksiyalarga ega sodda, ammo kuchli foydalanuvchi interfeysi bilan uyg'unlashgan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Ứng dụng bao gồm nhiều hàm toán học tích hợp và hỗ trợ các tính năng nâng cao như hàm do người dùng định nghĩa, số phức và chuyển đổi đơn vị. Tất cả được kết hợp với giao diện đơn giản nhưng mạnh mẽ, có xem trước kết quả tức thời, tô sáng cú pháp và tự động hoàn thành.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh">它内置许多数学函数并支持一些高级功能，例如用户定义函数、复杂数字和单位转换。这可配合简单又强大的用户界面，包括结果预览、语法高亮和自动完成。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">它包含多種內建數學函數，並支援進階功能，例如使用者自訂函數、複數與單位轉換。這些功能搭配簡潔但強大的使用者介面，提供即時結果預覽、語法醒目提示與自動補完。</p>

    <p>SpeedCrunch is available for several platforms in a number of languages.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يتوفر SpeedCrunch على عدة منصات وبعدد من اللغات.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">SpeedCrunch està disponible per a diverses plataformes en diverses llengües.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">SpeedCrunch je dostupný pro několik platforem v řadě jazyků.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">SpeedCrunch er tilgængelig til flere platforme på en række sprog.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">SpeedCrunch ist für verschiedene Plattformen in einer Anzahl von Sprachen verfügbar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το SpeedCrunch είναι διαθέσιμο για διάφορες πλατφόρμες σε πολλές γλώσσες.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">SpeedCrunch is available for several platforms in a number of languages.SpeedCrunch is available for several platforms in a number of languages.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">SpeedCrunch disponeblas por pluraj platformoj en kelkaj lingvoj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">SpeedCrunch está disponible para varias plataformas en varios idiomas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es_AR">SpeedCrunch está disponible para varias plataformas en varios idiomas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">SpeedCrunch on saadaval mitmele platvormile mitmes keeles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">SpeedCrunch hainbat plataformatarako eskuragarri dago, hizkuntza ugaritan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">SpeedCrunch برای چندین سکوی نرم‌افزاری و به چندین زبان در دسترس است.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">SpeedCrunch on saatavilla useille alustoille useilla kielillä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">SpeedCrunch est disponible sur plusieurs plateformes dans de nombreuses langues.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">SpeedCrunch זמין למספר פלטפורמות ובמספר שפות.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A SpeedCrunch számos platformra elérhető különböző nyelveken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">SpeedCrunch tersedia untuk beberapa platform dalam sejumlah bahasa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">SpeedCrunch è disponibile per diverse piattaforme in varie lingue.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">SpeedCrunch は複数のプラットフォームで、多言語に対応しています。</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">SpeedCrunch는 여러 플랫폼에서 다양한 언어로 사용할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">SpeedCrunch skaičiuotuvas yra prieinamas kelioms platformoms daugeliu kalbų.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">SpeedCrunch ir pieejams vairākām platformām vairākās valodās.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">SpeedCrunch er tilgjengelig for flere plattformer på en rekke språk.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">SpeedCrunch is beschikbaar voor verschillende platforms in een aantal talen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">SpeedCrunch jest dostępny na kilka platform w wielu językach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O SpeedCrunch está disponível para várias plataformas em diversos idiomas.SpeedCrunch está disponível para diversas plataformas e em várias línguas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_PT">O SpeedCrunch está disponível para várias plataformas em diversas línguas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">SpeedCrunch este disponibil pentru mai multe platforme în mai multe limbi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">SpeedCrunch доступен для нескольких платформ в ряде языков.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">SpeedCrunch je dostupný pre viaceré platformy v niekoľkých jazykoch.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">SpeedCrunch je na voljo za več platform v več jezikih.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">SpeedCrunch finns tillgänglig för flera plattformar på ett antal språk.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">SpeedCrunch, çeşitli dillerde birden çok platform için kullanılabilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">SpeedCrunch доступний для кількох платформ різними мовами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uz@Latn">SpeedCrunch bir nechta platformalar uchun ko'plab tillarda mavjud.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">SpeedCrunch có sẵn cho nhiều nền tảng với nhiều ngôn ngữ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh">SpeedCrunch 提供多种语言和平台。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">SpeedCrunch 可在多個平台上使用，並提供多種語言。</p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.speedcrunch.SpeedCrunch.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>speedcrunch</binary>
    <id>speedcrunch.desktop</id>
  </provides>

  <kudos>
   <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
   <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://heldercorreia.bitbucket.io/speedcrunch/_static/appdata-screenshots/0.12/advanced-features.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Main window with optional keypad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">النافذة الرئيسية مع لوحة أرقام اختيارية</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Finestra principal amb teclat numèric opcional</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno s volitelnou numerickou klávesnicí</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Hovedvindue med valgfrit numerisk tastatur</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Hauptfenster mit optionalem Nummernblock</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Κύριο παράθυρο με προαιρετικό αριθμητικό πληκτρολόγιο</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">Main window with optional keypad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Ĉefa fenestro kun nedeviga cifera klavaro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal con teclado numérico opcional</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es_AR">Ventana principal con teclado numérico opcional</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Põhiaken valikulise numbriklahvistikuga</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Leiho nagusia aukerako zenbakizko teklatuarekin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">پنجرهٔ اصلی با صفحه‌کلید عددیِ اختیاری</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Pääikkuna valinnaisella numeronäppäimistöllä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Fenêtre principale avec pavé numérique optionnel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">החלון הראשי עם לוח מספרים אופציונלי</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Fő ablak opcionális billentyűzettel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Jendela utama dengan keypad opsional</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Finestra principale con tastierino numerico opzionale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">オプションのテンキー付きメインウィンドウ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">선택적 숫자 키패드가 있는 기본 창</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Pagrindinis langas su pasirinktine klaviatūra</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Galvenais logs ar izvēles ciparu tastatūru</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Hovedvindu med valgfritt numerisk tastatur</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdvenster met optioneel numeriek toetsenblok</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno z opcjonalnym blokiem numerycznym</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Janela principal com teclado numérico opcional</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_PT">Janela principal com teclado numérico opcional</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Fereastra principală cu tastatură numerică opțională</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно с дополнительной клавиатурой</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Hlavné okno s voliteľnou numerickou klávesnicou</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavno okno z izbirno številčnico</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudfönster med valfritt numeriskt tangentbord</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">İsteğe bağlı sayısal tuş takımıyla ana pencere</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно з додатковою цифровою клавіатурою</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uz@Latn">Ixtiyoriy raqamli klaviaturali asosiy oyna</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Cửa sổ chính với bàn phím số tùy chọn</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh">主窗口（键盘可用）</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">主視窗（含選用數字鍵盤）</caption>
      <image>https://heldercorreia.bitbucket.io/speedcrunch/_static/appdata-screenshots/0.12/keypad.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The constants list and formula book</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">قائمة الثوابت وكتاب الصيغ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">La llista de constants i el llibre de fórmules</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Seznam konstant a kniha vzorců</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Listen over konstanter og formelsamling</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Die Konstantenliste und das Formelbuch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Η λίστα σταθερών και το βιβλίο τύπων</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">The constants list and formula book</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">La listo de konstantoj kaj formularo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La lista de constantes y el libro de fórmulas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es_AR">La lista de constantes y el libro de fórmulas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Konstantide loend ja valemiraamat</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Konstanteen zerrenda eta formula-liburua</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">فهرست ثابت‌ها و کتاب فرمول‌ها</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Vakioiden luettelo ja kaavakirja</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La liste des constantes et le livre de formules</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">רשימת הקבועים וספר הנוסחאות</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Az állandók listája és formula könyv</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Daftar konstanta dan buku rumus</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Lista delle costanti e formulario</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">定数リストと数式集</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">상수 목록 및 공식 모음</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Konstantų sąrašas bei formulių knyga</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Konstanšu saraksts un formulu grāmata</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Listen over konstanter og formelsamlingen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">De constantenlijst en het formuleboek</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Lista stałych i zbiór wzorów</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">A lista de constantes e o livro de fórmulas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_PT">A lista de constantes e o livro de fórmulas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Lista constantelor și cartea de formule</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Константы и формулы</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Zoznam konštánt a kniha vzorcov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Seznam konstant in knjiga formul</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Listan över konstanter och formelboken</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Sabitler listesi ve formül kitabı</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Список констант і збірник формул</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uz@Latn">Doimiylar ro'yxati va formulalar kitobi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Danh sách hằng số và sổ công thức</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh">常量列表和公式书</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">常數清單與公式手冊</caption>
      <image>https://heldercorreia.bitbucket.io/speedcrunch/_static/appdata-screenshots/0.12/constants+book.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Customizable user interface</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">واجهة مستخدم قابلة للتخصيص</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Interfície d'usuari personalitzable</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Přizpůsobitelné uživatelské rozhraní</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Brugerflade, der kan tilpasses</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Anpassbare Benutzeroberfläche</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Προσαρμόσιμο περιβάλλον χρήστη</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">Customizable user interface</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Agordebla uzantinterfaco</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Interfaz de usuario personalizable</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es_AR">Interfaz de usuario personalizable</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Kohandatav kasutajaliides</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Pertsonaliza daitekeen erabiltzaile-interfazea</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">رابط کاربری قابل سفارشی‌سازی</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Mukautettava käyttöliittymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Interface utilisateur personnalisable</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">ממשק משתמש הניתן להתאמה אישית</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Testreszabható felhasználói felület</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Antarmuka pengguna yang dapat disesuaikan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Interfaccia utente personalizzabile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">カスタマイズ可能なユーザーインターフェース</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">사용자 지정 가능한 사용자 인터페이스</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Tinkinama naudotojo sąsaja</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Pielāgojama lietotāja saskarne</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Tilpassbart brukergrensesnitt</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Aanpasbare gebruikersinterface</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Konfigurowalny interfejs użytkownika</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Interface de usuário personalizável</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_PT">Interface de utilizador personalizável</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Interfață de utilizator personalizabilă</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Настраиваемый пользовательский интерфейс</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Prispôsobiteľné používateľské rozhranie</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Prilagodljiv uporabniški vmesnik</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Anpassningsbart användargränssnitt</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Özelleştirilebilir kullanıcı arayüzü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Налаштовуваний інтерфейс користувача</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uz@Latn">Moslashtiriladigan foydalanuvchi interfeysi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Giao diện người dùng có thể tùy biến</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh">可定制用户界面</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">可自訂的使用者介面</caption>
      <image>https://heldercorreia.bitbucket.io/speedcrunch/_static/appdata-screenshots/0.12/ui-customization.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The built-in user manual</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">دليل المستخدم المدمج</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">El manual d'usuari integrat</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Vestavěná uživatelská příručka</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Den indbyggede brugervejledning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Das integrierte Benutzerhandbuch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Το ενσωματωμένο εγχειρίδιο χρήστη</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">The built-in user manual</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">La enkonstruita uzantmanlibro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">El manual de usuario integrado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es_AR">El manual de usuario integrado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Sisseehitatud kasutusjuhend</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Barneko erabiltzaile-eskuliburua</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">راهنمای کاربرِ داخلی</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Sisäänrakennettu käyttöopas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Le manuel d'utilisation intégré</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">מדריך המשתמש המובנה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Beépített kézikönyv</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Panduan pengguna bawaan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Manuale integrato</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">内蔵ユーザーマニュアル</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">내장 사용자 설명서</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Įtaisytas naudotojo vadovas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Iebūvētā lietotāja rokasgrāmata</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Den innebygde brukermanualen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">De ingebouwde gebruikershandleiding</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Wbudowany podręcznik użytkownika</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">O manual do usuário integrado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_PT">O manual do utilizador integrado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Manualul de utilizare integrat</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Встроенное руководство пользователя</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Vstavaná používateľská príručka</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Vgrajen uporabniški priročnik</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Den inbyggda användarhandboken</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Yerleşik kullanıcı kılavuzu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Вбудований посібник користувача</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uz@Latn">Ichki foydalanuvchi qo'llanmasi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Hướng dẫn sử dụng tích hợp</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh">内置用户手册</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">內建使用者手冊</caption>
      <image>https://heldercorreia.bitbucket.io/speedcrunch/_static/appdata-screenshots/0.12/manual.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://heldercorreia.bitbucket.io/speedcrunch</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bitbucket.org/heldercorreia/speedcrunch/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://heldercorreia.bitbucket.io/speedcrunch/introduction.html</url>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.0" date="2026-03-08"/>
    <release version="0.12" date="2016-11-29"/>
    <release version="0.11" date="2014-01-30"/>
    <release version="0.10.1" date="2008-06-03"/>
    <release version="0.10" date="2008-04-01"/>
  </releases>

  
  <languages>
    <lang>hu</lang>
    <lang>pt_PT</lang>
    <lang>pt</lang>
    <lang>de</lang>
    <lang>ko</lang>
    <lang>id</lang>
    <lang>he</lang>
    <lang>lt</lang>
    <lang>nl</lang>
    <lang>it</lang>
    <lang>zh</lang>
    <lang>ja</lang>
    <lang>fr</lang>
    <lang>ru</lang>
    <lang>et</lang>
    <lang>lv</lang>
    <lang>eu</lang>
    <lang>el</lang>
    <lang>es_AR</lang>
    <lang>en_GB</lang>
    <lang>fi</lang>
    <lang>ar</lang>
    <lang>pl</lang>
    <lang>uz@Latn</lang>
    <lang>es</lang>
    <lang>ca</lang>
    <lang>sk</lang>
    <lang>nb</lang>
    <lang>tr</lang>
    <lang>ro</lang>
    <lang>sv</lang>
    <lang>da</lang>
    <lang>cs</lang>
    <lang>vi</lang>
    <lang>en</lang>
  </languages>
</component>